Every resume should have a header that displays their name fully
每份简历都应有一个显眼的标题 将你的名字粗体显示
to help the employer recognize your resume from someone elses.
以帮助雇主将你的简历与他人的区分开来
It should contain the appropriate contact information and
标题部分应包含适当的联系方式
link to your other online profiles,
以及其他网上个人资料的链接
in case the employer wants to find out more about you.
方便雇主了解你的更多信息
Then the rest of your resume is about providing evidence that you are job
然后简历的剩余部分就是提供证据 证明你为求职
ready.
做好了准备
You want to include the education and work experiences you have.
你可以在其中包含教育背景和工作经验
If you feel like one of these sections will not be very strong,
如果你觉得自己在这两方面不够突出
emphasize others.
那就强调其他方面
When I was applying to my first job, I had no prior work experience.
当我应聘第一份工作时 我之前没有任何工作经验
I wrote a lot about my volunteer and student club roles to show
我写了很多自己参与过的志愿者和学生社团活动 以证明
I could work in a team, meet deadlines, and multitask.
我能够进行团队合作 遵守截止期限及处理多项任务
I also had a very large education section.
我的教育背景部分内容也很充实
Where I even listed an award I got I was 13,
我甚至在其中列出了我在 13 时获得的一个奖项
because I didn't have much else to show.
因为我其他方面的经验实在有限
By now I've held a few jobs so I've removed all of my volunteer roles.
现在 我已经从事过多个工作 所以我删掉了志愿者部分
And my education is the smallest and least important section on my resume.
我的教育背景也成了内容最少 重要性最低的简历部分
Good news, by completing program you won't have to desperately fill out your
好消息是 通过完成优达学城纳米学位项目 你便不必像我当年那样
resume like I did years ago.
无事可写了
By completing your core projects you will have relevant experience to share.
完成核心项目 你就拥有了可以分享的相关经验
The first thing an employer reads on a resume has to be the most relevant work
雇主在简历上最看重的是求职者与所应聘职位相关性最大的
a job candidate has.
工作经验
Prior jobs should be listed first if they're related to your new career.
与新职位相关的之前工作应列在最前面
If previous jobs aren't related, or
如果之前的工作不相关 或者
if you've never held a job, you can list your projects or education first.
你之前从没有从事过任何工作 可以将参与过的项目或教育背景列在前面
Depending on what provides the most evidence that you're job-ready.
取决于哪个最能证明你为求职做好了准备
You should also include a skill section that is a short list
你还应该包含技能部分 用一个简短的列表
summarizing all the skills you've developed in jobs, in projects, and
总结你在工作、项目和学习中获得的与你应聘的岗位
learning, that are relevant to the job you're pursuing.
相关的所有技能
These skills should be as technical as possible such as
这些技能应尽可能侧重技术方面 例如
being able to speak Spanish or Mandarin, or software programming skills.
会说西班牙语或汉语 或软件编程技能
You shouldn't include skills that employers assume someone already has or
最好不要包含雇主认为他人都会 或者
can learn easily, such as using Microsoft Word.
可以轻松习得的技能 例如使用 Microsoft Word
There are certain skills sometimes called soft skills
有些技能称为软技能
that are more effective when they're shown in examples.
这些通过例子来证明最有效
Don't list communication or teamwork, for example, as skills.
不要将沟通和团队合作能力之类的列为技能
Instead, demonstrate that you're a great communicator and
而是 在项目和工作经验部分的点句中
team player in the bullet points of your project and experience sections.
说明你有较好的沟通和团队协作能力
Let's dive into that next.
下面我们来深入讲讲这一方面